var myFlashcards = [     {question:"economic factors alone may provide motivation for the proposed combination",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/08/thompson-smithkline-gardner.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>thompson</b></span></a>'},{question:"if features of one reference cannot be combined into structure of the other may indicate nonobvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/orthopedic.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>orthopedic</b></span></a>'},{question:"The Examiners mere speculation is not a sufficient basis for a prima facie case of obviousness.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/warner-sporck.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>warner, sporck</b></span></a>'},{question:"if modification renders prior art unsatisfactory for intended purpose, no suggestion or motivation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/seachange-tec-air-haruna-gordon.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>gordon</b></span></a>'},{question:"A reference teaches away when POSITA, upon reading it . . . would be led in a direction divergent",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/seachange-tec-air-haruna-gordon.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>tec air, haruna</b></span></a>'},{question:"All words in a claim must be considered in judging the obviousness of the claimed subject matter",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/wilson-warner.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>wilson</b></span></a>'},{question:"For obviousness under 103, all that is required is a reasonable expectation of success.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/ofarrell.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>ofarrell</b></span></a>'},{question:"Synergism, in and of itself, is not conclusive of unobviousness in that synergism might be expected.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/kunzmann-kollman-lebounty-dwight-lloyd.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>kollman</b></span></a>'},{question:"examiner cannot use the invention as a template for its own reconstruction",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/sensonics-myers-jacoby-gorman.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>sensonics</b></span></a>'},{question:"ommission is preferred, so reliance on a large no. of refs does not weigh against obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/sensonics-myers-jacoby-gorman.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>myers, jacoby, gorman</b></span></a>'},{question:"absence of prima facie case of obviousness, if applicant complies with statutory req. entitled to a patent",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/rouffet.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>rouffet</b></span></a>'},{question:"mere fact prior art may be modified does not make it obvious unless prior art suggested it",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/fritch-gordon.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>fritch, gordon</b></span></a>'},{question:"burden of proof for prima facie case of obviousness in product by process claim lower",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/vehicular-kcj-harari-fessmann.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>fessmann</b></span></a>'},{question:"evidence to rebut prima facie case of obviousness must be commensurate in scope with claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/dill-dilnot.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>dill</b></span></a>'},{question:"addition of a method step in a product claim cannot impart patentability to an old product",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/dill-dilnot.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>dilnot</b></span></a>'},{question:"for prior art to teach away must discredit solution claimed, not just disclose different solution",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/fulton.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>fulton</b></span></a>'},{question:"reasonable expectation 103 comb. would yield successfully functioning device question of fact",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/ofarrell-medichem.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ofarrell, medichem</b></span></a>'},{question:"commensurate in scope (with claims) means reasonable basis untested embodiments behave in same manner",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/dill-lindner.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>dill, lindner</b></span></a>'},{question:"change in form or shape obvious design choice, unless achieves different purpose",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/trintec-robertson-oelrich-dailey-gal.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>dailey, gal</b></span></a>'},{question:"mere existence of differences not enough to establish nonobviuosness, must render unobvious to POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/janakiraman-ormco-muchmore-dann.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>dann</b></span></a>'},{question:"if narrow dependent claims are obvious, so are broader independent claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/janakiraman-ormco-muchmore-dann.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><b>janakiraman, ormco, muchmore</b></a>'},{question:"test for obviousness is what combined teachings would have suggested to POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/keller-ksr-kahn.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>keller</b></span></a>'},{question:"103 rejections need articulated reasoning with rational underpinning",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/keller-ksr-kahn.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>KSR, kahn</b></span></a>'},{question:"indefinite if fails to inform POSITA with reasonable certainty scope of invention.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/applied-materials-aller-antonie.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>nautilus, orthokinetics</b></span></a>'},{question:"discovering optimum, workable ranges inventive if not result-effective variables",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/applied-materials-aller-antonie.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>applied materials, aller, antonie</b></span></a>'},{question:"non-obviousness cannot be established by attacking references individually",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/thorpe-baxter-travenol-merck.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>merck</b></span></a>'},{question:"patentability doesn't depend on method of production",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/thorpe-baxter-travenol-merck.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>thorpe</b></span></a>'},{question:"known composition doesn't become patentable because described as somewhat inferior to another for same use",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/ricoh-fulton-gurley.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>gurley</b></span></a>'},{question:"to teach away reference must discourage or lead POSITA in divergent direction",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/ricoh-fulton-gurley.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>ricoh, fulton</b></span></a>'},{question:"obvious design choice precluded where claimed structure and function it performs different from prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/rose-chu.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>chu</b></span></a>'},{question:"the size of the article under consideration ... is not ordinarily a matter of invention.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/rose-chu.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>rose</b></span></a>'},{question:"103 rejection must rest on factual basis, no hindsight reconstruction and all facts must be considered.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/warner.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>warner</b></span></a>'},{question:"commercial success may be attributable to advertising and position as market leader before the introduction of the patented product",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/remark-demaco-pentec-mclaughlin.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>pentec</b></span></a>'},{question:"merely assering commercial success of article embodying invention sold by someone else insufficient.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/remark-demaco-pentec-mclaughlin.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>remark, demaco</b></span></a>'},{question:"extrinsic evidence may be used to explain but not expand meaning of ref relied on for anticipation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/schreiber-kloster-baxter-travenol.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>baxter travenol</b></span></a>'},{question:"proffered facts must be commensurate with claim scope",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/novo-impax-hiniker.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>hiniker</b></span></a>'},{question:"[i]nforming a patient about the benefits of a drug in no way transforms the process of taking the drug",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/merck-kao.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>kao</b></span></a>'},{question:"obvious to try rejected when multitude of effective combinations and no particular formulation less obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/merck-kao.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>merck</b></span></a>'},{question:"Obviousness is determined by considering what combined teachings of the references would have suggested to a routineer.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/oakley-moutette.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>moutette</b></span></a>'},{question:"Claim construction is a necessary predicate to an obviousness determination.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/oakley-moutette.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>oakley</b></span></a>'},{question:"popcorn machine and rowing machine, prior art must be capable of performing functional limitation, and not teach away",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/schreiber-giannelli.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>schreiber, giannelli</b></span></a>'},{question:"not necessary prior art be physically combinable",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/sneed-orthopedic-andersen-nievelt.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>sneed, orthopedic, andersen, nievelt</b></span></a>'},{question:"combination of known components resulting in an effect greater than the predicted additive effect may be nonobviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/wrigley-seattle-box-planet-bingo.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>wrigley</b></span></a>'},{question:"module not means-plus-function",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/baird-jones-merck-williamson.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>williamson</b></span></a>'},{question:"teach away' means line of development flowing from prior art unlikely to be productive of result sought by applicant",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/medichem-gurley-scientific-plastic-clay.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>medichem, gurley</b></span></a>'},{question:"analogous art two prongs (1) same field of endeavor (2) if not, reas. pertinent to part. prob.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/medichem-gurley-scientific-plastic-clay.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>scientific plastic, clay, innovention toys</b></span></a>'},{question:"motivation in the prior art to combine the references does not have to be identical to that of applicant to establish obviousness.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/kemps-lear-siegler-oelrich-par.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>kemps</b></span></a>'},{question:"artisan not compelled to blindly follow teaching of one prior art over another",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/kemps-lear-siegler-oelrich-par.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>lear siegler</b></span></a>'},{question:"An examination for unexpected results is a factual, evidentiary inquiry",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/mayne.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>mayne</b></span></a>'},{question:"finding source of problem may be patentable even if once found remedy obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/nomiya-typhoon-touch-vizio.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>nomiya</b></span></a>'},{question:"can't adopt claim construction beyond what is reasonable in light of totality of written description",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/baker-hughes-hampel-burhans.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>baker hughes</b></span></a>'},{question:"Defining the problem in terms of its solution reveals improper hindsight in the selection of the prior art relevant to obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/monarch-knitting.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>monarch knitting</b></span></a>'},{question:"not obvious if removal of a structure from prior art would undermine sole stated purpose of embodiment",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/larson.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>larson</b></span></a>'},{question:"nothing unobvious in choosing 'some' among 'many' indiscriminanately.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/lemin.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>lemin</b></span></a>'},{question:"extrinsic evidence ok to explain but not expand on meaning of ref in 102",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/baxter-travenol-netmoneyin-atmel.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>baxter travenol</b></span></a>'},{question:"selection of a known material based on its suitability for its intended use support[s] a prima facie obviousness determination",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/sinclair.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>sinclair</b></span></a>'},{question:"fact reference may be modified to reflect feature of invention not enough for obviousness, must have suggested desirability of such modification.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/mills.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>mills</b></span></a>'},{question:"making integral obvious unless shows insight contrary to understanding and expectations of the art.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/larson-fridolph-schenck-adams.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>larson, fridolph, schenck, adams</b></span></a>'},{question:"mere rearrangement of parts argument must not be impermissible hindsight reconstruction or mere conclusory statements",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/japikse-ksr.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>japikse, KSR</b></span></a>'},{question:"must demonstate invented species sufficient to support claim to functionally-defined genus",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/gordon-ariad-abbvie-rochester.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>ariad, abbvie, rochester</b></span></a>'},{question:"notice req. violated if rejection so uninformative prevents applicant from recognizing its grounds",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/jung-chester-jung.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>Jung, chester</b></span></a>'},{question:"rebut 103 falls within prior art range by (1) prior art taught away or (2) unexpected results",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/peterson-iron-grip-stepan.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>peterson, iron grip</b></span></a>'},{question:"prior art 'printed publication' depends on whether 'publicly accessible' during the prior period.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/bruckelmeyer.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>bruckelmeyer</b></span></a>'},{question:"anticipation if falls within prior art range; prima facie obvious if overlaps",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/atofina-harris-boesch-peterson.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>atofina, harris, boesch, peterson</b></span></a>'},{question:"motivation to combine doesnt have to come from prior art, and to modify can differ from applicants",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/warner-dystar-alcon.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>dystar, alcon</b></span></a>'},{question:"factual basis, no speculation, unfounded assumptions or hindsight reconstruction in 103",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/warner-dystar-alcon.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>warner</b></span></a>'},{question:"no requirement the prior art references used in a rejection must be analogous art to each other",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/innovention-toys.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>innovention toys</b></span></a>'},{question:"for 103 not necessary that the inventions of the references be physically combinable",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/sneed-schaumann-petering.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>sneed</b></span></a>'},{question:"A showing of unexpected results must be based on evidence, not argument or speculation.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/mayne.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>mayne</b></span></a>'},{question:"not 'design choice' if design achieves desired different functions different from the prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/gal-chu.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>gal, chu</b></span></a>'},{question:"if alleged commercial success would stem from a feature disclosed in the prior art there can be no nexus",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/tokai.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>tokai</b></span></a>'},{question:"only if considered desirable for any reason, is cutting integral structure into separable parts obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/merck-dulberg.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>dulberg</b></span></a>'},{question:"bald assertion of error without proposed altern. POSITA level not enough",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/okajima-litton-gpac-custom-accessories.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>okajima, litton, GPAC, custom accessories</b></span></a>'},{question:"mixing two conventional spray detergents prima facie obvious, organic-inorganic hybrid composite is not",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/kerkhoven.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>kerkhoven</b></span></a>'},{question:"unexpected results must show claimed invention exhibits superior property POSITA wld have found surprising",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/soni-baxter-travenol-applied-materials.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>soni</b></span></a>'},{question:"just because alternatives exist doesn't mean an inferior combination is inapt for obviousness purposes",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/winner-intl-mouttet.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>mouttet</b></span></a>'},{question:"for teaching away, the benefits both lost and gained should be weighed against one another",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/winner-intl-mouttet.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>winner intl</b></span></a>'},{question:"undue experimentation needs 'acceptable reasoning inconsistent with enablement.'",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/wright-wands-strahilevitz-amgen.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>wright, wands, strahilevitz, amgen</b></span></a>'},{question:"design choice rejection needs unexpected results or difference in function to be overcome",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/chu-catalina-rice.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>rice, chu</b></span></a>'},{question:"1st 3 factors are scope and content of prior art, difference between it and claims, level of ordinary skill,",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/graham.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>graham</b></span></a>'},{question:"design choice solves no stated problem and presents no unexpected result",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/kuhle-king.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>kuhle</b></span></a>'},{question:"if POSITA capable of performing operations with pencil and paper the steps performed are noninventive",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/lifescan.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>lifescan</b></span></a>'},{question:"disclosure of a genus in the prior art is not a disclosure of every species that is a member of that genus",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/atofina-lizardtech.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>atofina</b></span></a>'},{question:"finding of inherency in 103 is a high standard, limitation at issue necessarily must be present",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/par-pharmaceutical.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>par pharmaceutical</b></span></a>'},{question:"claimed dimensions that cause the claimed device to perform differently from the prior art are critical",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/gardner.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>gardner</b></span></a>'},{question:"failures of experimenters with no interest in succeeding not accorded great weight",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/reid-michalek-carroll.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>reid, michalek, carroll</b></span></a>'},{question:"combining familiar elements according to known methods obvious when does no more than yield predictable results",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/ksr.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>KSR</b></span></a>'},{question:"anticipation needs all elements disclosed arranged as in the claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/connell.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>connell</b></span></a>'},{question:"one cannot show nonobviousness of combination by attacking individual references",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/keller-carnegie-webster-loom.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>keller</b></span></a>'},{question:"mere statement of a new use for an old composition cannot render a claim to the composition patentable",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/zierden.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>zierden</b></span></a>'},{question:"two-prong test in chem, wld POSITA select prior art cmpd, reas. expec. of success to modify",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/otsuka-takeda-atofina.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>otsuka, takeda, atofina</b></span></a>'},{question:"simply appending general steps to abstract ideas performed by a computer not patent-eligible",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/alice-mayo-ovshinsky.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>alice, mayo</b></span></a>'},{question:"if modification would make prior art unsatisfactory for its intended purpose, no suggestion or motivation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/gordon.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>gordon</b></span></a>'},{question:"order in which the references are listed in the rejection makes no substantive difference",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/moutette.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>moutette</b></span></a>'},{question:"showing disclosure entials undue experimentation PTO's initial burden",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/armbruster-marzocchi-angstadt-sullivan.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>angstadt</b></span></a>'},{question:"for analogous art, Examiner must consult structure and function of claimed invention as perceived by POSITA.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/bigio-bigio-hyatt.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>bigio</b></span></a>'},{question:"analogous art same field of endeavor or reasonably pertinent to particular problem inventor is involved with.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/k-tec.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>k-tec</b></span></a>'},{question:"if prior art optimum values within outer limits of range, optimum values outside may not be obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/sebek-patel-sjolund-interval.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>sebek, patel</b></span></a>'},{question:"if not a result-effective variable, not obvious under Aller rule discovery of optimum value obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/aller-antonie.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>aller, antonie</b></span></a>'},{question:"Express suggestion to substitute one equivalent for another need not be present to render substitution obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/fout.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>fout</b></span></a>'}
     ];
